# Owolabi Toba Samuel

Fullstack Developer

Lagos, Nigeria +2348162977243,+2347061409595 owolabitoba31@gmail.com github.com/Thobatech31 linkedin.com/in/toba-owolabi-466316205

# **Summary**

**FullStack Developer** offering 3+ years of experience providing technical support to startups building digital solutions. Proficient in translating designs and wireframes into higher quality code and writing application interface code via Javascript, ReactJs workflows and also employed a variety of languages such as NodeJs, Javascript, PHP (FatFree), Html, Css and Bootstrap to write and create user-friendly web applications. Excels working in a team environment and ability to learn rapidly.

# **Experience**

FullStack Developer November 2019 - PRESENT

Elta-Solutions. Lagos State Nigeria.

Focusing on building web apps using reactJs and PHP (Fatfree).

- Developing the latest user-interface features using ReactJs and built reusable components for use.
- Optimizing components for maximum performance across a vast of web capable devices and browsers.
- ❖ Involved in architecting solutions along with other team members.

Intern Web Developer July 2016 - January 2017 Coven Works Ltd.

Intern Web Developer Coven Works Limited.

❖ Assisted in providing support and offering advice for all technical issues raised. Assisted in the creation of lander pages for adverts Rendered support for all computer based activities.

# Education

**Federal University of Technology Akure, Nigeria. 2013 - 2018** Bachelor of Technology, Computer science.

Second Class (Upper Division).

Carried a thesis on Platform As a Service (Paas) and Saas Architecture.

# **Academic Qualifications**

National Youth Service Corps. (N.Y.S.C) Discharge Certificate 2019 - 2020

# **Projects**

#### **Gamepride**

Link: <a href="https://gamepride.elta.solutions">https://gamepride.elta.solutions</a>

Admin Link: https://master.d1fw1hhg8f4mmy.amplifyapp.com/

Description: An online game platform to play against anyone, earn money and

earn respect.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **Expensa**

Link: <a href="https://develop.d3v4luort70rus.amplifyapp.com">https://develop.d3v4luort70rus.amplifyapp.com</a>

Admin Link: <a href="https://master.dtnyqynuddwqc.amplifyapp.com/">https://master.dtnyqynuddwqc.amplifyapp.com/</a>

**Description:** A financial Management Application.

2

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **Artsave**

Link: <a href="https://artsave.elta.solutions/">https://artsave.elta.solutions/</a>

Admin Link: https://artsave-admin.elta.solutions/

Description: An online game platform to play against anyone, earn money and

earn respect.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### <u>Agbedowo</u>

Link: <a href="https://agbedowo.com">https://agbedowo.com</a>

Description: An online agricultural fair-trader platform, connecting farmers to

industries all around the world.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **Swapify**

Link: <a href="https://www.swapiffy.xyz/">https://www.swapiffy.xyz/</a>

Description: An online platform that provides the fastest and most secure way to

exchange digital currencies.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **Auto Mart**

Link: https://627cbc8be5ef910008c215f3--prismatic-heliotrope-bb6388.netlify.app/

**Description:** An online marketplace for automobiles, wth auto mart users posting

their cars for sales.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **Ecommerce Shopify**

 ${\bf Link:} \underline{https:} //629 \underline{f644c9d52b814dd1805ba--willowy-otter-a382 \underline{f8.netlify.app}/$ 

**Description:** An online marketplace for Wears, users can order any type wears, watches, shoes etc.

#### **Recallomobile**

Link: <a href="https://recallomobile.elta.solutions">https://recallomobile.elta.solutions</a>

**Description:** A Call Management Application that was built to route inbound and

outbound calls intelligently for users.

Technology: ReactJs / Redux.

#### **CAC Checker App**

Link: https://company-checker.netlify.app

**Description:** An online App for verifying businesses using their CAC serial No.

**Technology:** ReactJs.

#### **Ecommerce Shopping Api's**

Link:https://documenter.getpostman.com/view/10804592/UVeAw9Bs#1925fa6 8-9afe-46ed-9514-bc6eef8250c1

**Description:** An online based ecommerce shopping platform to buy products and make a payment using Stripe payment gateway.

Technology: NodeJs.

## **ChurchSpace Api's**

Link: <a href="https://documenter.getpostman.com/view/10804592/UVkgwJjJ">https://documenter.getpostman.com/view/10804592/UVkgwJjJ</a>

**Description:** An Online web based platform where churches can manage their daily, weekly and monthly activities etc. and make use of Paystack and Dojah payment system

Technology: NodeJs.

## <u>Ropay</u>

Link: <a href="https://ropay.ng/">https://ropay.ng/</a>

**Description:** An Online web based platform to compute advance payroll, statutory compliance, automate salaries, pay employees, remit pension and disburse airtime for employees.

**Technology:** PHP (FatFree) / Javascript.

#### **Rohealth**

Link: <a href="https://rohealth.ng/">https://rohealth.ng/</a>

**Description:** An Online web based platform to **Give your employees greater** decision-making control over their health insurance, while at the same time saving your business 20–30% in costs.

**Technology:** PHP (FatFree) / Javascript.

#### **Evermissed**

Link: http://server.elta.com.ng/evermissed

 $\textbf{Description:} \ \textbf{An Online web based platform for honouring and celebrating}$ 

memorable lives.

Technology: PHP (FatFree).

## **Kedesa Whogohost**

Link: <a href="http://server.elta.com.ng/kedesa\_whogohost">http://server.elta.com.ng/kedesa\_whogohost</a>

Description: An Online web based platform to send Bulk SMS (messages),

Airtime etc.

Technology: PHP (FatFree).

#### **Church Management App**

Link: <a href="http://server.elta.com.ng/churchmanagementapp">http://server.elta.com.ng/churchmanagementapp</a>

**Description:** An Online web based platform where churches can manage their daily, weekly and monthly activities etc.

# **Core Competencies**

JavaScript,ReactJs,NodeJs,Mongoose, PHP, FatFree, Html, Git, CSS, Bootstrap, Material UI.